Guide to the Guerrilla TV Archive 1965-1997 MSS 138 MSS.138
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Oversize Materials: Series I, 55075
  - Bay Area Video Coalition (BAVC), undated; 55102 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Women's Video, undated; 55101 (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - Fred Simon, undated; 55100 (Box 17, Folder 71)
  - Stevenson Palfi, undated; 55099 (Box 17, Folder 74)
  - Mike Hazard, undated; 55098 (Box 17, Folder 77)
  - Miscellaneous Video Art, undated; 55097 (Box 17, Folder 85)
  - Video Artists A-L, undated; 55096 (Box 17, Folder 86)
  - Video Artists M-Z, undated; 55095 (Box 17, Folder 87)
  - Canadian Video, undated; 55094 (Box 17, Folder 89)
  - Alvarez, Kolker and New Orleans Video Access Center (NOVAC), undated; 55093 (Box 17, Folder 91)
  - Jon Alpert articles and catalogues, undated; 55092 (Box 17, Folder 93)
  - Appalshop, undated; 55091 (Box 17, Folder 95)
  - Ithaca Video Festival, 1981-1995; 55090 (Box 17, Folder 110)
  - Mobius Video, San Francisco, undated; 55089 (Box 17, Folder 114)
  - New Orleans Video Access Center (NOVAC), undated; 55088 (Box 17, Folder 116)
  - Optic Nerve, undated; 55087 (Box 17, Folder 121)
  - Paper Tiger TV, Deep Dish TV and DeeDee Halleck, undated; 55086 (Box 17, Folder 122)
  - Paul Ryan, undated; 55085 (Box 17, Folder 132)
  - TVTV Conventions, undated; 55083 (Box 17, Folder 141)
  - San Francisco Video Festival, 1983; 55084 (Box 17, Folder 133)
  - TVTV Adland, undated; 55082 (Box 17, Folder 148)
  - Video Free America, undated; 55081 (Box 17, Folder 152)
  - Videofreex, Media Bus, Lanesville, undated; 55080 (Box 17, Folder 153)
  - Miscellaneous and Details: Display Selection, undated; 55079 (Box 17, Folder 157)
  - Miscellaneous and Details: Video and TV Newspaper Articles, undated; 55078 (Box 17, Folder 161)
  - Cable and Public Access TV: Basic Cable, undated; 55077 (Box 17, Folder 163)
  - Cable and Public Access TV: National Federation of Local Cable Programmers (NFLCP), undated; 55076 (Box 17, Folder 166)
- Oversize Materials: Series V, 55072
  These boxes contain oversized materials from Series V: Photographs, primarily large format photographs and images used in the book Subject to Change: Guerrilla Television Revisited
  - Paper filed amid video stills. [corresponding photographs located in boxes 8 and 9], undated; 55074 (Box 17, Folder 261)
  - Photographs and Images used in Subject to Change: Guerrilla Television Revisited, undated; 55073 (Box 17, Folder data_value_missing_d1df31bc9b27e0428714a0232612bbbc)
- Oversize Materials: Series VIIIB, 55064
  Oversize materials from Series VIIIB: Printed Materials primarily include large newspapers and magazines.
  - CineVue [Asian Cinevision], 1988; 55071 (Box 18, Folder 298)
  - Community Video Report, 1974; 55070 (Box 18, Folder 301)
  - Current, September 1988, 55069 (Box 18, Folder 302)
  - The Independent Gazette, July 1976, 55068 (Box 18, Folder 308)
  - The Television Laboratory at WNET-13: Vision News, Winter 1977, 55067 (Box 18, Folder 316)
  - Video Guide, Nov.'78-Jan.'79, 2:4-5, 3:2, 5:1, 5:2, ca. 1980; 55066 (Box 18, Folder 320)
  - Video Tools #1 and #2, photocopies, 1972-1973; 55065 (Box 18, Folder 321)